(Sheldon:)-I'm not accepting the award.
-Why not?
(Howard:)Turns out the great Sheldon Cooper
has stage fright.
(Penny:)That's no reason to back out.
(Penny:)I once got a pretty big
honor in high school.
(Penny:)I was terrified about appearing
in front of a big crowd...
(Penny:)...but I went through with it.
You know?
(Penny:)The world looked pretty darn good
sitting on a haystack...
(Penny:)...in the back of a Ford F-150 as a
member of the corn queen's court.
Thank you. I'll bear that in mind...
(Sheldon:)...if I'm ever nominated
for the Hillbilly Peace Prize.
(Leonard:)-Sheldon, you're being ridiculous.
-Am I?
(Sheldon:)Let me tell you a story.
(Howard:)Where's 70 children
when you need them?
(Sheldon:)I was 14 and graduating
summa cum laude from college.
"Summa cum laude" is Latin
for "with highest honors."
(Penny:)I just love how you always skip over
the part where no one asks.
(Sheldon:)I was valedictorian
and expected to give an address.
(Sheldon:)Even now I can remember
that moment...